CURRICULUM VITAE

Kgosi Rasebitse

071 568 1369/082 770 3549/ Kgosi.rasebitse240@gmail.com



♣ Gender: Male

Address 16 Bell road, Claremont

Languages: English, Afrikaans

Marital Status: Single

Nationality: South African

♣ Notice Period: 1 Month

PROFILE

Dynamic team player with an ability to work independently. Adaptable to changing priorities and effective under pressure. Excellent interpersonal skills and a budding iOS enthusiast fueled by a passion for crafting captivating mobile experiences.

I have a solid foundation in software development and a knack for creative problem solving.

I would describe myself as a highly motivated individual who continuously perseveres to ensure success.

EDUCATION

2023 – In progress iOS Developer course (Online learning): Udemy

2023 – Ongoing Hyperion Dev (Online learning)

2021 - Completed Matric: Cedar House High School

SKILLS & COMPETENCIES

- Effective verbal and written communication skills.
- Testing and Quality Assurance.
- Team cohesiveness.
- Excellent interpersonal skills.

COMPUTER SKILLS/LANGUAGES

- Swift Programming
- ♣ Xcode
- ♣ iOS SDK
- ♣ Swift UI
- Ulkit

ACHIEVEMENTS

■ 2022 – Shortly after Matriculating traveled into Europe in pursuit of finding employment as a Deck hand. Landed in France and a few days later took a train to Antibes the coast of France by train to hand out my CV's, did that for almost a month with no luck. Thereafter decided to try my luck in Palma Spain, Ibiza, Lisbon Portugal and lastly Madrid in Spain. After months of job searching and not securing anything made my way back to SA in June. This has to be one of my most liberating, nerve wrecking and exciting experiences all at the same time thus far.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Rain South Africa

Date: July 2023 to date
Position Held: Junior iOS Developer

Job Purpose

I am responsible for the designing, developing, and maintaining applications specifically tailored for Apple's iOS platform.

Key Responsibilities

- Develop and maintain iOS applications.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.
- Ensure the performance, quality, and responsiveness of applications.
- Identify and correct bottlenecks and fix bugs.
- Help maintain code quality, organization, and automatization.
- Stay up to date with new technologies and best practices in mobile development.

Reasons for wanting to leave: Looking to further develop myself in a new environment.

Date: July 2022 to date
Position Held: QA Tester

Job Purpose

I was responsible for testing gap analysis between requirements and existing environments accurately for all rain software systems internal and external.

Key Responsibilities

- Test software applications to ensure they meet quality standards and user requirements.
- Identify, document, and track bugs and issues found during testing.
- Collaborate with developers and project managers to resolve issues and ensure timely delivery of high-quality software.
- Develop and execute test cases, scripts, plans, and procedures.
- Participate in requirements analysis and review sessions to ensure testability of features.
- Provide feedback on usability, functionality, and performance of applications.
- Stay updated on testing tools, techniques, and best practices.